Hey, everyone. Team Rocket here.
This is a demo for the Devpost
OpenAI WebMCP Challenge.
To start things off, Team Rocket is a
collection of six AI-powered builds
/ applications,
each exploring how people and agents
can collaborate on the open web.
We did implement WebMCP
across all applications.
In order to see exactly how we did this,
you can take a look over here.
And as you can see, we used
a total of 44 tools
across six builds,
six of which wait for human confirmation.
This is where that collaboration
comes into play.
And as you can see here as well,
we did build in safety mechanisms
to keep everything safe and aligned.
And if you scroll down, you can see
what tools are accessible from what page,
which ones are accessible from all pages,
and a little bit more detail about
exactly what's going on here,
along with a red tag to see
what needs human input.
So, without further ado,
we're going to go ahead and demo
these WebMCP tool calls by using
the Taskboard app.
So, I'm going to go ahead and ask
the agent to open that application up.
And to just give some brief explanation
on Taskboard app, it is an application
that helps organize tasks into a
Kanban-style board.
The idea here is that the agent
can work with humans to collaborate
on tasks, update tasks, delete tasks,
and so forth.
All right, so here is the first page.
As you can see, you can give it a goal
and a rough timeline.
For the next phase,
I'm going to go ahead and ask
the agent to build this out for us.
And as you can see on the top,
you can see that the agent
is using the Taskboard's
set_goal tool,
and right beside it, you can see
the amount of tools that are
available to the agent.
So, here it looks like it is
breaking the tasks down into
a Kanban-style board.
We'll give that a few minutes—
or a few seconds, I should say.
All right, looks like the board went ahead
and was generated.
Now, we can use the agent to read
what's on the board.
But before that, as you can see here,
we have a progress bar
and a Kanban-style board down here
with Not Started, In Progress, and Done.
So, for the purpose of this demo,
we're just going to go ahead and ask
the agent to read the stages
of the tasks, which is one
of the WebMCP tools we implemented.
And again, at the top, you can see
what tool it's accessing,
and then a current progress
over here on the left.
Right. So, now we can go ahead
and try out some of the other
WebMCP tools.
For the next part, we're just going to
ask it to move something
across the board.
Right. And so, the write demo script /
draft demo script is going to be moved
over to Done since that's completed.
And as you can see in the interface,
it has been moved and the progress bar
has been updated.
Now, for the next task,
I'm going to go ahead and do something
a little bit more riskier, which is to
delete a task in order to see
how the confirmation gate is implemented.
So, here we're just going to try to remove
the record footage and voiceover.
And as you can see,
this confirmation gate appears
at the bottom, asking for human input.
I'm going to go ahead and confirm it,
and we did see the deletion
of that task.
So, from here, I'm going to go ahead
and move on.
And in lieu of the time remaining,
I'm just going to go ahead and wrap
the demo up by saying that
this was just an example
of one of the many applications
on the Team Rocket control hub
that can use WebMCP.
We do see this as an option for
humans and agents to collaborate
across useful product features,
such as the taskboard tasks
that we just witnessed.
Thank you all for your time,
and we'll see you at the next one.